votefromabroad.org 2016-11-28

# Privacy | www.votefromabroad

[VoteFromAbroad.org](http://votefromabroad.org/) is a nonpartisan voter registration tool provided as a public service by Democrats Abroad.

Democrats Abroad is committed to protecting your privacy online. Democrats Abroad does not retain any sensitive personally identifiable information such as your social security number, driver’s license number, or passport number. Democrats Abroad maintains aggregate data for statistical purposes. Democrats Abroad will not use any information provided to us here for any other purpose unless we first obtain your consent.

  Democrats Abroad will hold any information you provide us here with the utmost care and will only use it in ways to which you have consented: for preparation of the voter registration materials in all cases; and, according to your expressed consent, for voting reminders and information, for contact from Democratic candidates, or for membership in Democrats Abroad, as the case may be.

  All personal information and other unique identifiers required by law for voter registration that are submitted in the process of registering to vote are used to produce the voter registration form to send to your local or state election officials. If you opt in to join Democrats Abroad, you will have given us permission to transfer your name, contact information, birth date, and voting state information to the Democrats Abroad membership database. For information about the privacy policy for personal data about members of Democrats Abroad see [https://www.democratsabroad.org/privacy_statement](https://www.democratsabroad.org/privacy_statement).

Democrats Abroad does not share member information with Democratic candidates or Democratic Party organizations without your explicit consent.  If you opt to receive information from Democratic candidates, you will have given us permission to transfer your name, contact information, and voting state information to the campaigns of Democratic candidates and the associated Democratic state parties.

  Like any other voter at in the U.S., once you mail in your voter registration application form to your local or state election officials, it becomes a matter of public record and is available for inspection and use by legitimate candidates for public office and their campaign organizations as well as by others who satisfy the requirements of the State law governing its use.

Any information that you provide will be collected and maintained directly on servers located in the United States and operated by Overseas Vote Foundation and/or by Democrats Abroad. If you are located outside the United States, any information you provide will be transferred to the United States. Democrats Abroad is committed to maintaining your information with all legally required protections. You should know, however, that the general level of protection for personal information in the United States may not be the same as that provided in other countries.

  If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site, or your interaction with this website, send email to: [Help@votefromabroad.org](mailto:Help@votefromabroad.org) or contact us by postal mail at:

Democrats Abroad  
PO Box 15130  
Washington, DC 20003, USA

Public Service provided by Democratic Party Committee Abroad ([DemocratsAbroad.org](http://democratsabroad.org/)). 

This communication is not authorized by any candidate or candidate's committee.
